# Aradhana Dash

Pune, Maharashtra, India



aradhana.dash1997@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/aradhna-221

### **Summary**

I am a Skilled Content Marketing executive driven to develop successful content assets and marketing plans that satisfy clients and meet demanding objectives. First-rate attention to detail and creative mindset. As a content marketing executive and intern, I have worked for various clients in marketing automation, software development, medical coding, and tax automation.

### **Experience**

#### **Content Marketing**

The Smarketers

Apr 2021 - Present (3 months +)

Creating Content Strategy for clients.

Content calendar creation for internal content assets.

Creating and editing various content assets in different formats like blogs, Ebooks, Landing pages,

White papers, LinkedIn Ad copies, Video scripts, and Quora and Reddit optimization.

Established workflow for requesting, creating, editing, publishing, and retiring content.

## Content trainee

Rizzle

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 (4 months)

Content Trainee at Rizzle. Worked with their US outreach team.

## **Example 2** Creative Associate

LMN Media

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020 (2 months)

Brainstorming campaign strategies for clients.

Social media content for various clients.

Copywriting and editing for Social media posts.

Content strategy Innovative Incentives and rewards, Delhi.

Fostered a highly communicative, collaborative team culture on all visual product projects.

## 😱 Social Media Marketing Intern

Innovative Incentives & Rewards Pvt. Ltd.

Jul 2020 - Aug 2020 (2 months)

Working on the Social media content calendar for Innovative Incentive's page On LinkedIn, Twitter, and Instagram.

Copywriting for social media posts.

Social media management.

#### **Skovian** Intern

Skovian

Apr 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

Content Marketing and SEO Content Writing.

Social Media Strategy and Copywriting.

Boosted reach by creating digital content, managing schedules, maintaining social media accounts, and reporting analytics to measure engagement.



#### Ex: content writing intern

**IBI** Group

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018 (3 months)

- · Content writing for annual report, award nomination, event flyers.
- News tracking.
- · Drafting press releases.
- Media management at events, event coordination.
- · Citizen engagement events; Organized flash mobs, street plays in collaboration with various educational institutions to raise awareness about social issues.

#### **Education**



### SYMBIOSIS INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Public Relations/Image Management 2019 - 2021



#### XAVIER UNIVERSITY, BHUBANESWAR

Bsc Mass communication, none 2015 - 2018



#### D.A.V Public School

High School, Science 2013 - 2015

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



#### Content Marketing - HubSpot Academy

Issued Jun 2021 - Expires Jul 2023 8a8718245ebd4a81b68ef7b9d5ad9352

#### Skills

News Writing • Television Studio Production • Corporate Communications • Microsoft Office • Public Relations • Journalism • Digital Media • Media Planning • Content Marketing • Digital Marketing